I'll tell you more about Chrome, new tap extension that actually works.
Even though in the previous videos, you've already realized that the music hacker tapped
new devs on an app and a new tap.
By default, it's not opening a Google, but hacker tap when I can see, like, trending
repositories of GitHub, trending, Reddit posts, trending hacker news articles, poverty
data, that actually takes from one of the sources and shows the most interesting articles
from hishnow, medium, product hunt, and yeah, I can switch between those sources here.
So we see dev2, free code, lobsters, medium, even seshnowed in the hackers.
All right, so this is how it works, and people are using it.
I prepared other alternatives, so this is the one that the music hacker tapped feature
thrown at nine, and basically I'm using every day, but there is a crypto tapped.
So I will show you how you can actually use it, Chrome exports a manifest scheme.
Chrome, you have a rights that less extension, replace the browser, new tap page with
a page you bundle in the extension, and the next extension can only overwrite one of the
Chrome special pages.
So practically, you ship HDMI, CSS JavaScript page inside the next extension, sometimes you
can actually implement a redirect approach, and that page is shown every time the users
open a new tab, because it's with us so often, it's a primary last date.
So in support of platform constraint, because Chrome now is using manifest frame, that means
background-resistant pages were replaced by a service worker model.
So it's like even service worker lifecycle, and some API's behaviors has changed.
And we need to plan it.
We can obviously monetize this new tab, but how it can monetize, for example, Google
has explicit rules and increase scrutiny around, around affiliate links, injecting ads or
anything that change the user browsing experience or collect data, so you have to follow
starware browser, and now we cannot even monetize it directly within the Chrome dashboard.
So we have to use external service such as Stripe.
So this is a crypto tab, and when I edit this from extension, I can install it, it has
been installed.
Now when I open it, by default, did you want to change it?
So I can change it back, it would go back default to hacker tab, and now you skip it.
So this is a pretty simple, I can look, so I see it's new tab, and I like this as an extension,
and keep that in mind if you want to see like a source code, we can use Chrome, source extension.
So now I can open it up, see our Explorer, and see a lot of the code, so if you're interested
how the API is specified, you can search it here, see we're on an adapter, browse extension,
API fake, and API skip, but even though when you are on the extension as a new tab here,
we can see it's like open source, so we see it like open source extension, crypto tab,
and API.
And when you go to API, we'll be redirected to Bitcoin price API that we can use.
And given the start, we can test it out.
It wasn't updated, but as you can see, it's still working basically, it just gets the
price of the Bitcoin when we open, so if you're not interested in like a trading daily,
but for example, you open sometimes, and you want to see how it looks per day, and the
price, and you see the time, we can use it.
And if it gets worth dimension, there are many extension that works as a new tab for trading,
and you can see like a stocks here in best fellow, and they're not so popular, so I think
it's a nice niche, especially when you have to be like your own tracker, or maybe tracker
sim later, so there are not many of them, this stock level, things for Chinese users, and
some other one.
Obviously, you can download it, you can scrap it, and see actually what is invested and
changed.
There are other type of extensions, and there are productivity tab that may close it.
So this is just a crypto tab, but yeah, we can still use it.
So when I try to use unreproductive to new tab, I will be added here, and in the meantime,
I will just remove that crypto tab, I don't need this, and I will just remove.
And now it's unary, so when I open a new tab, now I will set keep it, and as you can see,
I can switch to the languages, you have a tiny, creamy, tiny, I want to do this on my
language polish, but I will use English by default, and there are some folders, customization,
amount, takes, and just give me a product step, okay, we can use it.
And here we can just customize Chrome for each tab, so there is like a toolbar and footer
that we can recreate, and we see like some places that we can use, so you can click
plus, and we have many things that we can do like a total list, and then I will save,
and then I can specify some total list directly here.
And I can extend, make it bigger, smaller, so it will go and directly change between those,
and when we are ready, we can just specify it here at home.
Here we can add like a test description, so if I hit first, I see it.
I can just switch it, and possible to add like a widget, I can save it, I can remove it,
and if you are not interested, because me press S, and if you want to add another one,
so we go here, click plus, and we can add another one, so like a picture, maybe Anki
for something, and like a deck, obviously we have to configure, but if you are learning
languages, you can do like assistant status, so you can get like a CPU load, so it will
check for our CPU load, you can change for another one, like a top site that I visit,
or like quick links, so we can add permission to the top site, you can grant, and when
I allow it, it will really feel, so I have my Discord Twitter, I have my investing platform,
and we can go for another one, so this is like a weather map, so just add a weather, and
now we can switch the city and win speed, so if you're like in New York, United States
and Save it, and press enter, we will get the temperature, okay, I can now open a new
temperature, we see the map and I, so we have a calculator to this, we have a nodes, this
is actually very great, because we can add a recess fit for a specific channel, and there
are different types like a bookmark, a bookmark group, an embedded webpage, a recess, so you
can add, but for developers and designers, we can add just like a design, and see the new
information that I came from here, it's really nice, an extendable extension, and the
bookmarks, everything is in that spot list, it's great, and it's very extendable, I
really like the six tensions, an orange, a nice, and I think it's one of the most popular,
if you go to settings, you can get like a help, import, export, change theme, something
else, and just colors, folders, are all general things, and this is the new tab, how
I had to crumb, and I will remove no annery, as it goes, I don't want to have overlapping
usually, obviously, we are supposed to have only one, so I will remove it, and a goodbye
friend, okay, and now we just keep it, waste your languages, finish editing, and now we
use grid, and here we can like adjust for our grids, but they're not visible, there are
some links, we can enter nodes, and on the left we can add like a carances, so like exchange
rates, but as you can see, we have to specify an API here, right, in order to get this information
top side, so probably to show the top sides, so we have to grant like a permission,
and then you show the top size that I have visited, it's like a T-B-D, stocks, Facebook, and other
platforms, see the weather, progress throughout the app, progress bar, okay, so we see the
kind of progress bar of the year, which is very important, if only 14% left until 2026,
this is my age, okay, and getting older, it's similar to annery, but as you can see there is a
demon for it, and you can adjust it for your purpose, and last but not least there's like a new
top widgets, I will still use it, and we will create like a mini horoscope on your tab, so now if I
remove a new tab, and I will install a new top widget, be able to get it, okay, we get it, so now I can
open a new tab, I will keep it, it looks similar when we create a new widgets, I think it's still
an hour, it has the most beautiful design, but here is the option to add something like JPG in the
dark dashboard, Gmail, as you can see some of the widgets are pro, so this is how you can get some
monetization stuff, so it's nice, maybe some people are paying for this, actually it's the first one
that we see that is monetizing, so we have a memory room widget, and this really we can actually see,
so it's nice, we can create it for our purpose, everything is worth the motion that some of this
information can be pro, and this way we can monetize and just ask for a small price, this is like
one steam directly from your tab page, it's actually very nice, so when you have a steam account,
it will basically directly open or like go with slides and other stuff, I think it's nice,
especially if you have so many bookmarks, you can make like the short bookmarks here,
to be able to speed up your process of your work and it detects my time. I'm in Bangkok now.